Got an idea
you need to
test dependably on budget and yesterday?
Get the data and insights
you need on new products,
services, ads and more
in as little as 24 hours.
Your first decision:
Qual or Quant?
Rich insights or statistical validation?
Digsite does both.
It's called flexibility.
For the first time
you have Qual
and Quant capabilities
in one integrated platform.
We call it Sprints
for qualitative iteration
and Pulse for quantitative validation.
Let's say
you start with a pulse
to test
a new product concept,
use one of our templates
or make your own.
Choose how you want to engage people
with surveys,
image markup, voting
or fill in the blank stories.
Pulse tells you
which ideas are the winners,
allowing you to benchmark your results
to prior tests.
Now, your team has a ton more questions
to bring that winning idea to life.
Create a Sprint
and dive deeper
to optimize them with a Qual study.
Explore by asking questions
in a variety of ways.
Use live video interviews.
Have conversations,
share photos and videos,
and create chats
to follow up on answers.
You're always in the know
and in control with our smart dashboard.
Go full
DIY, full service
or choose a hybrid approach.
It's easy to get started
with super fast recruiting
using our proprietary social
find targeting
or our million household
plus national panel.
Bottom line,
cut your research timelines in half,
get more research for your budget
and make better decisions.
Oh, and get extras like automated
reporting straight to PowerPoint
so you're not up at 2:00 a.m.
with your preso.
You're welcome.
Get the data and insights
you need to keep innovating fast,
Digsite, insights for innovators.